<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Adrien's Dashbook</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Adrien's Dashbook</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 11:50:27 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bienvenue on my website</title><link>/posts/first-post/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 11:50:27 +0100</pubDate><guid>/posts/first-post/</guid><description>This site serves as my journal, on which I share things that intrigue me, as well as my portfolio, where I publish the different (academic) papers I&amp;rsquo;ve written, or my resume.
Please don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to contact me if you have any advices or comments ;)</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>/about/about/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 16:03:14 +0100</pubDate><guid>/about/about/</guid><description>Bienvenue!
I am a Swiss-French student presently enrolled a Joint Master’s degree in Cybersecurity (Computer Science) between the Swiss Federal Institutes of Technology in Lausanne (EPFL) and Zurich (ETHZ), since September 2023. While pursuing my Master’s degree, my main interests were Cryptography, Information Security, Software Security, Privacy Engineering, Machine Learning and Network Security. Prior to that, I completed my Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science with an emphasis on Software Engineering, Theory of Computation and Mathematics, at EPFL between 2020 and 2023.</description></item><item><title>Building a robust test suite of type confusion vulnerabilities</title><link>/writings/type-confusions/type-confusions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/writings/type-confusions/type-confusions/</guid><description>This paper was written under the supervision of Nicolas Badoux and Prof. Doc. sc. ETH Mathias Payer from HexHive Lab at EPFL and is available in PDF format on this repository.
&amp;ldquo;Before I came here I was confused about this subject. Having listened to your lecture I am still confused. But on a higher level.&amp;rdquo; - Enrico Fermi
Abstract C++ has a lot of vulnerabilities due to type confusion, which can lead to memory corruption and security vulnerabilities.</description></item></channel></rss>